<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://rebellion.global/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://rebellion.global/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-09-03T14:07:51+02:00</updated><id>https://rebellion.global/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Extinction Rebellion</title><subtitle>This is Our Declaration of International Non-Violent Rebellion Against the World’s Governments for Criminal Inaction on the Ecological Crisis.
</subtitle><author><name>ExctinctionRebellion</name></author><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Global Day of Action for the Amazon</title><link href="https://rebellion.global/events/2019/09/02/global-day-of-action-for-the-amazon/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Global Day of Action for the Amazon" /><published>2019-09-02T10:11:30+02:00</published><updated>2019-09-02T10:11:30+02:00</updated><id>https://rebellion.global/events/2019/09/02/global-day-of-action-for-the-amazon</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rebellion.global/events/2019/09/02/global-day-of-action-for-the-amazon/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/21/world/americas/amazon-rainforest.html&quot;&gt;Unprecedented&lt;/a&gt; fires are ravaging the Amazon - more than 74,000 fires this year is an 84% increase over last year’s count. This is an international tragedy and a dangerous contribution to climate chaos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This devastation is directly related to President Bolsonaro’s anti-environmental &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.climatechangenews.com/2019/01/22/brazils-natural-resources-open-business-bolsonaro-says/&quot;&gt;rhetoric&lt;/a&gt;, which erroneously frames forest protections and human rights as impediments to Brazil’s economic growth. Farmers and ranchers understand the president’s message as a license to commit arson with wanton impunity, in order to aggressively expand their operations into the rainforest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[VISIT &lt;a href=&quot;http://amazonwatch.org/amazonfires&quot;&gt;AMAZONWATCH.ORG/AMAZONFIRES&lt;/a&gt; FOR ACTION TOOLKITS TO HELP YOUR EVENTS]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amazon destruction is not new, however. Indigenous people of the Amazon have been &lt;a href=&quot;https://amazonwatch.org/news/2019/0509-terra-livre-propels-brazils-indigenous-movement-to-the-forefront-of-bolsonaro-resistance&quot;&gt;sounding the alarm&lt;/a&gt; about risks to the rainforest for years and &lt;a href=&quot;https://amazonwatch.org/news/2019/0801-as-the-brazilian-amazon-burns-indigenous-peoples-take-a-stand&quot;&gt;resisting the destruction&lt;/a&gt; - sometimes at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://amazonwatch.org/news/2019/0729-amazon-watch-condemns-murderous-invasion-of-brazilian-indigenous-territory&quot;&gt;cost of their own lives&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The National Articulation of the Indigenous Peoples of Brazil (APIB) has called for international solidarity in response to the fires and ever-increasing threats. Amazon Watch and Extinction Rebellion are leading a call for a Global Day of Action for the Amazon on September 5, 2019, also known as “Amazon Day.” Please join us!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gather in community to organize non-violent direct actions including, protests, sit ins, marches and vigils. You can also organize a benefit concert or film screening to raise much-needed funds to protect the Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is critical that before the G7 Summit, the United National General Assembly meeting and Climate Week, this issue be put on the forefront and that international pressure is brought to force Brazil to address the urgent need to suppress the fires, protect the Amazon and respect the rights of indigenous peoples and their territory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On September 5th we call on the global community to take action at Brazilian embassies or consulates and at the offices of the corporations profiting from Amazon destruction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Governments and companies around the world are emboldening Bolsonaro’s toxic policies when they enter &lt;a href=&quot;https://amazonwatch.org/news/2019/0809-a-trump-bolsonaro-free-trade-agreement-is-an-apocalyptically-bad-idea&quot;&gt;trade agreements&lt;/a&gt; with his government or &lt;a href=&quot;https://amazonwatch.org/news/2019/0603-more-pathetic-excuses-from-blackrocks-ceo&quot;&gt;invest in agribusiness companies&lt;/a&gt; operating in the Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amazon Watch and APIB conducted an &lt;a href=&quot;https://amazonwatch.org/news/2019/0425-complicity-in-destruction-2&quot;&gt;investigation&lt;/a&gt; this year that showed how many US and European companies - like Cargill and ADM - and financiers - like BlackRock, JP Morgan Chase and Santander - are complicit in Amazon deforestation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please sign up here to join actions planned for your area or arrange your own action and invite members of your network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sponsors:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://amazonwatch.org/&quot;&gt;Amazon Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rebellion.global/&quot;&gt;Extinction Rebellion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://apib.info/apib/?lang=en&quot;&gt;National Association of Indigenous Peoples of Brazil (APIB)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>ExctinctionRebellion</name></author><summary type="html">Unprecedented fires are ravaging the Amazon - more than 74,000 fires this year is an 84% increase over last year’s count. This is an international tragedy and a dangerous contribution to climate chaos. This devastation is directly related to President Bolsonaro’s anti-environmental rhetoric, which erroneously frames forest protections and human rights as impediments to Brazil’s economic growth. Farmers and ranchers understand the president’s message as a license to commit arson with wanton impunity, in order to aggressively expand their operations into the rainforest. [VISIT AMAZONWATCH.ORG/AMAZONFIRES FOR ACTION TOOLKITS TO HELP YOUR EVENTS] Amazon destruction is not new, however. Indigenous people of the Amazon have been sounding the alarm about risks to the rainforest for years and resisting the destruction - sometimes at the cost of their own lives. The National Articulation of the Indigenous Peoples of Brazil (APIB) has called for international solidarity in response to the fires and ever-increasing threats. Amazon Watch and Extinction Rebellion are leading a call for a Global Day of Action for the Amazon on September 5, 2019, also known as “Amazon Day.” Please join us! Gather in community to organize non-violent direct actions including, protests, sit ins, marches and vigils. You can also organize a benefit concert or film screening to raise much-needed funds to protect the Amazon. It is critical that before the G7 Summit, the United National General Assembly meeting and Climate Week, this issue be put on the forefront and that international pressure is brought to force Brazil to address the urgent need to suppress the fires, protect the Amazon and respect the rights of indigenous peoples and their territory. On September 5th we call on the global community to take action at Brazilian embassies or consulates and at the offices of the corporations profiting from Amazon destruction. Governments and companies around the world are emboldening Bolsonaro’s toxic policies when they enter trade agreements with his government or invest in agribusiness companies operating in the Amazon. Amazon Watch and APIB conducted an investigation this year that showed how many US and European companies - like Cargill and ADM - and financiers - like BlackRock, JP Morgan Chase and Santander - are complicit in Amazon deforestation. Please sign up here to join actions planned for your area or arrange your own action and invite members of your network. Thank you! Sponsors: Amazon Watch Extinction Rebellion National Association of Indigenous Peoples of Brazil (APIB)</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://rebellion.global/assets/content/2019/09/05/global-day-of-action-for-the-amazon-thumb.jpg" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">XR Phoenix Formational Meeting</title><link href="https://rebellion.global/events/2019/09/01/xr-phoenix-formational-meeting/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="XR Phoenix Formational Meeting" /><published>2019-09-01T01:13:30+02:00</published><updated>2019-09-01T01:13:30+02:00</updated><id>https://rebellion.global/events/2019/09/01/xr-phoenix-formational-meeting</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rebellion.global/events/2019/09/01/xr-phoenix-formational-meeting/">&lt;p&gt;We will be in Meeting Room A. We are meeting to organize a Phoenix chapter of XR (Extinction Rebellion). We will be planning to organize protests for the worldwide XR actions on Sept 20th, Oct 7th and for on-going actions. Please contact us if you want to be notified in advance of the agenda and/or put items on the agenda.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt; document.write('&lt;a style=&quot;unicode-bidi: bidi-override; direction: rtl;&quot; href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#97;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;&amp;#58;xrphoenix&amp;#64;protonmail&amp;#46;com &quot;&gt; moc&amp;#46;liamnotorp&amp;#64;xineohprx&lt;/a&gt;');&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Facebook event: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/364966161107165/&quot;&gt;https://www.facebook.com/events/364966161107165/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ExctinctionRebellion</name></author><summary type="html">We will be in Meeting Room A. We are meeting to organize a Phoenix chapter of XR (Extinction Rebellion). We will be planning to organize protests for the worldwide XR actions on Sept 20th, Oct 7th and for on-going actions. Please contact us if you want to be notified in advance of the agenda and/or put items on the agenda. Email: Facebook event: https://www.facebook.com/events/364966161107165/</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://rebellion.global/assets/content/2019/09/07/Sept-7th-FB-Banner-thumb.jpg" /></entry><entry xml:lang="de"><title type="html">Strassenfest für das Überleben</title><link href="https://rebellion.global/events/2019/09/01/strassenfest-fur-das-uberleben/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Strassenfest für das Überleben" /><published>2019-09-01T01:13:30+02:00</published><updated>2019-09-01T01:13:30+02:00</updated><id>https://rebellion.global/events/2019/09/01/strassenfest-fur-das-uberleben</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rebellion.global/events/2019/09/01/strassenfest-fur-das-uberleben/">&lt;p&gt;Stopp mal! Klimakrise - war da was?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Am 13. September wollen wir das Leben feiern und uns für das Überleben einsetzen. Gemeinsam werden wir einen Nachmittag lang in der Hamburger Innenstadt eine Straße besetzen und damit zeigen: Wenn Hamburg keinen Spurt für die Klimaziele hinlegt, legen wir den geregelten Ablauf in Hamburg lahm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dies ist unsere Ankündigung einer gewalt­freien, friedlichen Aktion des zivilen Unge­horsams. Bringe all deine Freude am Leben, deine Straßenkreide, deine Sopranstimme und Handklampfe, dein Märchenbuch und deine Seifenblasen mit auf die Straße!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bitte sorge dabei auch für dich und denke an es­sentielle Dinge wie genug Wasser, Wetter­schutz und Verpflegung.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bei einem der nächsten Aktionstrainings kannst du dich vorbereiten und eine Be­zugsgruppe finden, mit der du dich bei der Aktion aufgehoben fühlen kannst:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://extinctionrebellion.de/veranstaltungen/hamburg&quot;&gt;https://extinctionrebellion.de/veranstaltungen/hamburg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wenn deine Bezugsgruppe an der Aktion teilnehmen möchte, freuen wir uns auf eine Nachricht deiner Delegierten an&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&gt; document.write('&lt;a style=&quot;unicode-bidi: bidi-override; direction: rtl;&quot; href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#97;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;&amp;#58;hamburg+1309&amp;#64;extinctionrebellion&amp;#46;de &quot;&gt; ed&amp;#46;noillebernoitcnitxe&amp;#64;9031+grubmah&lt;/a&gt;');&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Schreibt uns, wie viele Rebell:innen ihr seid und ob ihr eine Übernachtungsmöglichkeit in Hamburg benötigt. Alle weiteren Details werden dich über deine Delegierte erreichen – zur rechten Zeit am rechten Ort!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alle, die nach den Prinzipien und Werten von Extinction Rebellion handeln, sind will­kommen, dieses Fest mit uns zu feiern.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wir freuen uns auf euch!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love &amp;amp; Rage&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;XR Hamburg&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ExctinctionRebellion</name></author><summary type="html">Stopp mal! Klimakrise - war da was? Am 13. September wollen wir das Leben feiern und uns für das Überleben einsetzen. Gemeinsam werden wir einen Nachmittag lang in der Hamburger Innenstadt eine Straße besetzen und damit zeigen: Wenn Hamburg keinen Spurt für die Klimaziele hinlegt, legen wir den geregelten Ablauf in Hamburg lahm. Dies ist unsere Ankündigung einer gewalt­freien, friedlichen Aktion des zivilen Unge­horsams. Bringe all deine Freude am Leben, deine Straßenkreide, deine Sopranstimme und Handklampfe, dein Märchenbuch und deine Seifenblasen mit auf die Straße! Bitte sorge dabei auch für dich und denke an es­sentielle Dinge wie genug Wasser, Wetter­schutz und Verpflegung. Bei einem der nächsten Aktionstrainings kannst du dich vorbereiten und eine Be­zugsgruppe finden, mit der du dich bei der Aktion aufgehoben fühlen kannst: https://extinctionrebellion.de/veranstaltungen/hamburg Wenn deine Bezugsgruppe an der Aktion teilnehmen möchte, freuen wir uns auf eine Nachricht deiner Delegierten an Schreibt uns, wie viele Rebell:innen ihr seid und ob ihr eine Übernachtungsmöglichkeit in Hamburg benötigt. Alle weiteren Details werden dich über deine Delegierte erreichen – zur rechten Zeit am rechten Ort! Alle, die nach den Prinzipien und Werten von Extinction Rebellion handeln, sind will­kommen, dieses Fest mit uns zu feiern. Wir freuen uns auf euch! Love &amp;amp; Rage XR Hamburg</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://rebellion.global/assets/content/2019/09/13/XR_IR_Day1__Waterloo_TheLightscaper_15-04-19-.width-1280.jpg" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Flood the streets of Malmö!</title><link href="https://rebellion.global/events/2019/07/30/flood-the-streets-of-malmo/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Flood the streets of Malmö!" /><published>2019-07-30T04:13:30+02:00</published><updated>2019-07-30T04:13:30+02:00</updated><id>https://rebellion.global/events/2019/07/30/flood-the-streets-of-malmo</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rebellion.global/events/2019/07/30/flood-the-streets-of-malmo/">&lt;p&gt;On August 24, Extinction Rebellion Sweden will carry out what they expect to be their biggest action yet. We’re going to flood the streets of Malmö!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This action is an important part of our strategy to force those in power to tell the truth about the scale of the climate and ecological emergency we face, and then to act accordingly to address it. It is also part of our build-up towards the October Rebellion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The action will take place at several targets in the Malmö area, and the meeting point will be in Kungsparken at 11 am. There will be training available here for any newcomers and anyone else who needs refreshing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From there, everyone will split up into groups and swarm various locations around Malmö. At the end we join up for a groovy festival blockade near the sea – the exact location of which will be disclosed closer to the date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will also be lots of music, arts, and fun!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Camping will be set up nearby for those who wish to do so, and other accommodation will be available. Please see the separate accommodation post (to come).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Facebook event will be updated with more details regarding travel, training and other preparations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are able to participate, we urge you to plan to attend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lets-flood-the-streets&quot;&gt;LET’S FLOOD THE STREETS!&lt;/h2&gt;</content><author><name>ExctinctionRebellion</name></author><summary type="html">On August 24, Extinction Rebellion Sweden will carry out what they expect to be their biggest action yet. We’re going to flood the streets of Malmö!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://rebellion.global/assets/content/2019/07/30/flood-the-streets-xrmalmo.jpg" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Rebel without Borders!</title><link href="https://rebellion.global/events/2019/07/30/rebel-without-borders/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rebel without Borders!" /><published>2019-07-30T04:13:30+02:00</published><updated>2019-07-30T04:13:30+02:00</updated><id>https://rebellion.global/events/2019/07/30/rebel-without-borders</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rebellion.global/events/2019/07/30/rebel-without-borders/">&lt;p&gt;Life on Earth is experiencing an unprecedented global crisis: Scientists agree – we face flooding, forest fires, extreme weather conditions, crop failure and the collapse of societies. The time of denial is over. It is time to act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Politics and conventional approaches to political engagement such as voting, lobbying, petitions and demonstrations fail to address this crisis. History shows us a promising, democratic means to bring about social change: nonviolent, civil disobedience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the 7th of October we will block cities through an international rebellion and thus halt everyday routines that destroy our livelihoods. Besides Berlin, Amsterdam, London, Paris and New York are at the center of the peaceful uprising. We will be thousands embarking on non-violent civil disobedience so that the government can finally respond appropriately to the climate crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will rebel together in streets and squares and remain there- peacefully, creatively and colorfully. Be part of it!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ExctinctionRebellion</name></author><summary type="html">Life on Earth is experiencing an unprecedented global crisis: Scientists agree – we face flooding, forest fires, extreme weather conditions, crop failure and the collapse of societies. The time of denial is over. It is time to act.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://rebellion.global/assets/content/2019/07/30/rebel-without-borders.jpg" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">International Solidarity Rebel Ride for action on the climate emergency</title><link href="https://rebellion.global/events/2019/07/30/international-solidarity-rebel-ride-for-action-on-the-climate-emergency/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="International Solidarity Rebel Ride for action on the climate emergency" /><published>2019-07-30T04:13:30+02:00</published><updated>2019-07-30T04:13:30+02:00</updated><id>https://rebellion.global/events/2019/07/30/international-solidarity-rebel-ride-for-action-on-the-climate-emergency</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rebellion.global/events/2019/07/30/international-solidarity-rebel-ride-for-action-on-the-climate-emergency/">&lt;p&gt;Cities around the world are hosting bike rides for climate on September 8th. The XR MA chapter will meet to ride at 3pm and end with a picnic (around 5).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;XR non-biking families and friends are invited to join us for music and fun at the picnic. Spread the word!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will meet on the Boston Common near the corner of Beacon and Charles St. We’ll ride together at an easy pace (7-8 mph) and tour the major areas of downtown Boston, occasionally pausing to notice a high watermark for areas that will be underwater in a few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We return to the Common at around 5pm to meet with family and friends for a picnic (near Frog Pond on the Beacon St. Side). Bring your own food, snacks or sweets to share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class=&quot;fucxed-green&quot; id=&quot;accessibility&quot;&gt;Accessibility&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any (partially) human powered vehicle capable of ~ 8 - 10 mph&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://xrmass.org/action/climate-ride-19/&quot; class=&quot;btn-xl o-button-green&quot;&gt;Subbbscribe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ExctinctionRebellion</name></author><summary type="html">Cities around the world are hosting bike rides for climate on September 8th. The XR MA chapter will meet to ride at 3pm and end with a picnic (around 5).</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://rebellion.global/assets/content/2019/09/08/international-solidarity-rebel-ride-for-action-on-the-climate-emergency.jpg" /></entry></feed>